Please, Knuckle! I beg you!
That son of a bitch,
the way he looked at me,
it was like… it was like…
I was nothing more than trash!
[crying] When you find him…
punch that bastard for me!
Yeah, I got this.
Sorry, Master,
but the thing is, we're both idiots.
Some things are more important
than saving the world.
[singer singing in English]
[singer singing in Japanese]
so that it wouldn't be destroyed.
However, it was blown
to the left of its original location.
It was precariously balanced,
[roars]
to take advantage of me
before I explode.
That's the only thing I can do.
[narrator] Then, all of a sudden,
approximately
100 trillion microorganisms,
in intervals that were
completely imperceptible
to Morel, were slowly,
but surely escaping,
In the basement
north of the palace
Marcos had told them
precisely where to go,
and so Ikalgo drove there
along the length
of the five-kilometer tunnel
in a commandeered truck.
By the time Ikalgo
had reached the crossroads
that led to wings A and B,
a satellite dragonfly
had already arrived at the warehouse…
It's likely that Bizeff
rushed after her,
and in his haste, he forgot to lock it.
[gasps]
[narrator] This was bad news.
For Ikalgo,
it meant a confrontation
with Bloster was unavoidable.
[heart beating]
[Ikalgo] Bloster suspects me.
Why? Did I make
some kind of mistake?
Stay calm. Stay calm,
and try to figure out what it is
he could have noticed.
[tires screeching]
I have to survive.
What happened
during our encounter
that aroused his suspicion?
Was there something off
about my imitation of Flutter?
There must have been.
but he didn't want to question me
right then and there,
because the evidence against me
wasn't conclusive enough
to warrant an accusation.
That's why he's come down here,
to see if his doubts were accurate.
Was it trivial enough
that I can talk my way out of this,
or was it so serious
I should assume the worst.
[Flutter's voice]
Is there anyone here?
or I'm dead meat.
Sinker Belle, if you're here,
I need you to come
with me at once!
[narrator] In reality,
proving that he was a trusted ally.
Why didn't you respond
when I called out?
Where did everyone else go?
[woman] I'm sorry.
I don't know anything
about what's happening outside.
The director says
that I can't speak to anyone,
and that I'm only
ever allowed to talk to him.
[narrator] It was obvious
that she thought this restriction
All of the other women
thought the same thing.
A messenger didn't make sense,
because there was
a direct phone line
that Bizeff used to contact them.
and to continue following orders.
Convinced that failing this test
would be unacceptable
to the director,
they each flatly refused
to speak to Ikalgo.
He would have liked to spare
the women from further danger,
but he had
neither the time nor energy.
[gasps]
[Ikalgo] There. Nen writing.
but even so, he could not
shake the persistent feeling
that he had lost a part of himself.
[Ikalgo] Palm.
If Palm got herself killed
or something else
has taken her out of commission,
use the Satellite Dragonflies
and your telepathy
to provide backup to the Ants.
Got it?
Yeah, I got it.
Just pretend
you're reporting to your superior,
when you're really
informing Meleoron instead.
You want me to feed them all lies
so that we can throw them off?
Yeah, and it's vitally important.
I'm counting on you.
[Ikalgo] That'll only work
assuming Meleoron and I
haven't been found out
to be double agents yet.
And since Bloster
is already suspicious of me,
I've gotta do something about it.
I have to take him out!
Huh?
Hey! Did you finish
your job from Hagya?
[Flutter's voice] Yeah.
I guess you could say that.
[Bloster] Hagya, huh?
Huh?
I could have sworn
he got mad when we called him that.
[gasps]
[tense music playing]
[shudders]
[suspenseful music playing]
[Ikalgo] They think the suspect's dead.
Once Bloster informs the others
of what he saw,
I'll be able to move around freely.
But still, I had no idea
that Hagya had changed his name.
If I end up
crossing paths with them,
I've gotta come up
with a better excuse.
No. That won't work.
Bloster didn't waste time
asking questions before he attacked.
Anyone who doesn't know
what Hagya's new name is,
[automated voice]
Please enter your code number.
Huh?
[Ikalgo gasps]
The elevator's not going up.
Don't tell me.
Did he really come down here
This is my chance.
I only have two options.
[Knuckle] Almost five minutes
since I activated
Hakoware: Bankruptcy Chapter Seven.
The aura debt will reach 7,000
before much longer.
All I have to do
is avoid a direct assault.
[gasps]
The worst-case scenario
is if I can't do that
and the hit's big enough
to terminate Hakoware
and deal me significant damage.
If that's what's gonna happen,
I'm better off
buying as much time as I can
and wait for him to go bankrupt.
Shoot's in bad shape.
He'll never last that long.
I have to make him explode
one more time.
If I don't, it's gonna be too late.
If I can't make this happen,
Shoot'll be dead
before the battle ends!
[Menthuthuyoupi] He fell for my trap.
Good. Looks like my fake rage
did the trick.
I've been looking for you,
you cockroach.
Now make this damn fly shut up!
Every damn time it squeaks at me,
But if I can just stay calm
when my rage takes over,
I should be able
to control my growth.
When he tries to take advantage
of the opportunity I give him,
It's not gonna happen, you idiot.
It's over.
You're gonna die on your knees,
I guarantee it.
Wait for it.
Just you wait.
[chuckles]
It's time.
You have accrued interest.
[dramatic music playing]
[Knuckle] This is gonna work.
To be perfectly honest,
I didn't even like him that much.
In fact, I always thought
he was kind of annoying.
I don't get it. Since when
did he become my best friend?
That's definitely a factor.
Risking your life
alongside someone else
He'll pay for that!
He walked away from someone
who put their life on the line
before their fight was even over!
Where the hell
is his code of honor, huh?
His code as a warrior?
You damn Ant!
Now I'm getting really pissed off!
One more punch,
but this one's for me!
Wow, I'm pretty awesome.
I don't think my mind
has ever thought this fast before,
and I'm still
in the middle of my punch.
Hold on.
Wait.
Isn't this that thing they talk about,
[tense music playing]
[angelic choir singing]
[Knuckles grunts] Crap!
He stopped swelling midway through!
[chuckles]
[Knuckle] He got me.
This whole time,
he was just playing me.
I can't stop.
Sorry, Shoot.
Looks like I screwed this up.
This'll be way more than the interest.
I can feel it.
I'm done for.
[choir singing continues]
Shoot, boss, everyone,
[man] Thunderbolt!
Now's my chance!
[electricity crackles]
[roars]
If you're not all big,
I can take you out! No problem!
[Menthuthuyoupi groans]
[upbeat music playing]
I even saw the pearly gates!
And now, I've gotta
get Shoot to a hospital.
Yeah!
I hit him eight times!
Whoo-hoo!
I didn't notice
there was an attack coming
from a different direction.
This annoying thing was on me
before I realized it.
I saw him on the stairs before.
[grunts]
[electricity crackling]
[singer singing in Japanese]